

CONTACT

A Jamie Leviner

Florence, SC 29501

(843) 229-1193

🖊 levinerjamie@gmail.coi

jamieleviner.com

SKILLS

JavaScript

VueJS

CSS/LESS/SASS

C#/ASP.NET MVC

PostgreSQL

JAMIE LEVINER

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

For the past 5 years, I have worked as a full stack software engineer with a concentration on front-end architecture, frameworks, and tooling. I am strongly interested in becoming part of a development culture that improves and enables its people, and I am looking forward to facing some new challenges.

EXPERIENCE

Software Engineer - ACS Technologies

July 2017 - present

Programming and watching cute cat videos.

Software Engineer-Associate - ACS Technologies

July 2016 - July 2017

Fulfillment of extremely important tasks.

Software Development Apprentice - ACS Technologies

August 2015 - July 2016

Making coffee and baking cookies.

Intern - ACS Technologies

May 2015 - August 2016

EDUCATION

Francis Marion University, Florence, SC 29501

Jan 2011 - Dec 2014

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science

Minor in Applied Mathematics